{
    "accordion_items": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Why was the developer angry at the compiler?",
        "answer": "Because it kept giving him null points!"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Why do programmers prefer dark mode?",
        "answer": "Because light attracts bugs!"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
        "answer": "Because he used up all his cache!"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
        "answer": "Because he didn't know how to 'null' his emotions!"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Why did the database administrator leave his wife?",
        "answer": "She had one too many triggers!"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Why did the CSS developer go to therapy?",
        "answer": "Because his styles were not aligned!"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Why did the QA engineer go to jail?",
        "answer": "Because he was caught in a loop hole!"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Why did the developer go to the beach?",
        "answer": "To surf the net!"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Why was the software developer afraid of the dark?",
        "answer": "Because he didn't know how to handle the light mode!"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Why did the C# developer get locked out of his house?",
        "answer": "Because he lost his keys with no reference!"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Why did the programmer always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
        "answer": "Because Oct 31 equals Dec 25!"
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Why did the programmer hang his phone on the wall?",
        "answer": "Because he wanted to make a mobile website!"
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Why did the programmer quit his job?",
        "answer": "Because he didn't get arrays!"
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Why was the code like a baby?",
        "answer": "Because it had a lot of bugs to be fixed!"
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Why was the developer always cold?",
        "answer": "Because he left his Windows open!"
      }
    ]
  }
  